<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Koliber</string>
    <string name="About_app">App is providing live, historical and forecast data about pollution and weather based on user\'s location. Data comes from external providers, developer is not responsible for any incorrect data. Created by Krzysztof Kobiałka in Kraków, Poland. Open-source and free to use under the MIT license.</string>
    <string name="pollution_sources">All the data comes from www.aqicn.org. The World Air Quality Index project is a non-profit project started in 2007. Its mission is to promote air pollution awareness for citizens and provide a unified and world-wide air quality information. The project is providing transparent air quality information for more than 130 countries, covering more than 30,000 stations in 2000 major cities, via those two websites: aqicn.org and waqi.info.</string>
    <string name="license">Copyright © 2021 Krzysztof Kobiałka. Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the Software), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions: The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED AS IS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">MapsActivity</string>
</resources>